

+79779481908 (Telegram, WhatsApp, Viber) mikhail.epatko@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/mikhail-epatko
htpps://github.com/MikhailEpatko
skype: mikhail.epatko

Profile

Java Software Engineer with over 3 years of successful experience in backend software development. Strengths in Java and Spring Boot framework backed by self training and training in lots of courses.

Skills			
Java	*******	Gradle	*****
Spring Boot	*******	Apache Ignite	*****
Apache Kafka		Google Guice	
Cassandra	*****	OpenAM	
JUnit		PostgreSQL	
Mockito		Liquibase	
Maven	*******	Docker	*****

Experience

Java Software Engineer, MTS Group

February 2020 – Present Moscow, Russia

Development of Access Management System, providing single sign-on (SSO).

Designing solutions together with an architect and front-end developers. Full development cycle of the server side of applications, their integration with each other and with external services. Writing autotests, fixing bugs. Code refactoring, development and improvement of the existing code base. Interaction with other teams to improve services and expand functionality. Conducting a code review.

Used languages, frameworks and technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Spring WebFlux, Apache Kafka, Cassandra, JUnit, Mockito, Maven, Git, Apache Ignite, OpenAM, Google Guice.

Java Software Engineer, Paragon Software Group

August 2018 - February 2020

Moscow, Russia

Development of: CRM and ERP business automation systems, connectors to the payment systems (PayPal, Alipay, Ingenico), warehouse system.

Used languages and frameworks: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring MVC, Hibernate, JavaScript, React.js, RabbitMQ, Apache Kafka, PostgreSQL, Redis, Liquibase, Docker, JUnit, Mockito, Maven, Gradle, Git, TeamCity.

Java Software Developer, Natalie Tours

November 2017 - June 2018

Moscow, Russia

Development of: recommendation system, mailing system, promotions constructor, system for make analitics, in-memory cache, research of the possibility of using machine learning for the recommendation system.

Used languages and frameworks: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, JDBC, JavaScript, Hibernate, Apache Maven, Gradle, JUnit, Mockito, Apache Kafka, Telegraf, Lua, Docker, GitLab CI, PostgreSQL, Clickhouse, Cassandra, Redis, InfluxDB, Tarantool, Python, R.

Java Software Developer, job4j company

October 2016 - October 2017

Remote

Development of: company site backend, site parser, net filemanager, chat, chat-bot.

Used languages and frameworks: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, JDBC, Hibernate, Apache Maven, JUnit, Mockito, PostgreSQL.

Education

MA in Jurisprudence

Vladivostok State University of Economics and Service 2000 – 2005

Certifications

JSON Processing with Java EE

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Spring: Test-Driven Development with JUnit

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Docker: Continuous Delivery

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Java Memory Management

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Learning GraphQL

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Extending, Securing, and Dockerizing Spring Boot Microservices

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Gradle for Java Developers

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Spring: Spring Cloud

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Spring: Framework In Depth

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Learning JUnit 5

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Java EE: Concurrency and Multithreading

LinkedIn Learning 2019

Algorithms and Data Structures

Stepic.org 2018

Basic statistics

Stepic.org 2018

Modern combinatorics

Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology 2018

Mashine learning

Mail.ru 2018

Mashine learning

Yandex 2018

Java SE8. Level 1. Java fundamentals

Computer Training Center "Specialist" at Bauman MSTU 2016

Operating system Linux

National Open University "INTUIT" 2015

Computer architecture and assembly language

National Open University "INTUIT" 2015

Operating system UNIX

National Open University "INTUIT" 2013